Guide to the Bella Abzug papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VII: Public Statements
  - Subseries VII.5: Speeches and Remarks, 1970-1974 (1981 Add.)
    - Peace and Priorities Coalition (D.C.) 21 January 1971 (Box 759A)
    - Women's National Press Club 27 January 1971 (Box 759A)
    - American University 2 March 1971 (Box 759A)
    - Democratic Caucus 13 March 1971 (Box 759A)
    - Lincoln Center Synagogue 19 March 1971 (Box 759A)
    - Democratic Council 2 April 1971 (Box 759A)
    - Park River Independent Democrats 29 April 1971 (Box 759A)
    - Urban Research Corporation (Americana) 14 May 1971 (Box 759A)
    - Cleveland City Club (barnstorming) 7 May 1971 (Box 759A)
    - Project Find Senior Citizens Conference 2l May1971 (Box 759A)
    - Local 1199 (Federal Plaza) 1 October 1971 (Box 759A)
    - Women's Strike for Peace, Evanston, Ill. 10 October 1971 (Box 759A)
    - Women's Caucus of Michigan 23 October 1971 (Box 759A)
    - New Era Club (Educational Alliance Bld.) 30 October 1971 (Box 759A)
    - St. Louis Jewish Forum 31 October 1971 (Box 759A)
    - University Of Pennsylvania 5 November 1971 (Box 759A)
    - New Chelsea Democratic Club 12 November 1971 (Box 759A)
    - Texas Bill of Rights 2l November 1971 (Box 759A)
    - Americans for Progressive Israel 24th Annual Hanuka Dinner 12 December 1971 (Box 759A)
    - U Thant Ceremony 18 December 1971 (Box 759A)
    - National Women's Political Caucus Fundraiser, Washington DC 3 February 1972 (Box 759A)
    - Women's Education for Delegate Selection Conference, Nashville 12 February 1972 (Box 759A)
    - N.Y. State Women's Political Caucus 4 March 1972 (Box 759A)
    - Americans for Democratic Action, Phila. 7 April 1972 (Box 759A)
    - Statement on Paris Trip 20 April 1972 (Box 759A)
    - United Auto Workers Convention, Atlantic City 27 April 1972 (Box 759A)
    - Free Synagogue, New York 16 May 1972 (Box 759A)
    - Fordham University Graduation 3 June 1972 (Box 759A)
    - Tufts University Graduation 5 June 1972 (Box 759A)
    - Election Night Statement 20 June 1972 (Box 759A)
    - B'nai B'rith Inwood Senior Citizens 18 March 1973 (Box 759A)
    - Florida Atlantic University, Boca Raton 13 April 1973 (Box 759A)
    - Community Conference 5 May 1973 (Box 759A)
    - National Welfare Rights Organization 12 July 1973 (Box 759A)
    - Ad Hoc Committee to Save our Children 26 July 1973 (Box 759A)
    - Gloria Karp Rally 23 September 1973 (Box 759A)
    - National Women's Political Caucus 20 October 1973 (Box 759A)
    - Women in Politics, Harper College, Ill. 8 November 1973 (Box 759A)
    - National Organization for Women/Marriage and Divorce 19 January 1974 (Box 759A)
- Series VIII: Printed Materials
  - Articles by or about Abzug: (Box 760)
    - Copies of journals, mostly loose (Box 760)
    - List of journals contained in box (Box 760)
    - Clippings and reprints about Abzug--1 folder (Box 760)
  - Articles by or about Abzug .(1981 Addition) (Box 760A)
  - Books inscribed to Abzug, (5 volumes) (Box 761)
  - Advance review proofs, (2 volumes) (Box 761)
  - Bella Abzug by Doris Faber, New York, Lothrop, Lee 1976. Inscribed to the patrons of Columbia University (Box 761)
  - Libraries by Bella S. Abzug (Box 761)
  - Journals, pamphlets and other printed items--1 box, mostly loose (Box 762)
  - Miscellaneous clippings--1 folder (Box 762)
  - Miscellaneous printed items--1 folder (Box 762)
- Series IX: Photographs
  - 1972-[1975] (Box 763)
  - [1975]-Indochina (Box 763)
  - 1975--[Cambodia]--Photographs, card and insignia removed from album (Box 763)
  - See also: Boxes 294, 325 (De1afie1d-General), 391 (Thanh), 394, 478 (Parks-Correspondence), 524 (Box 763)
  - (Greenburgh), 625 (Box 763)
  - Photographs which relate to specific subjects rather than to Abzug personally are filed with the subjects. (Box 763)
- Series X: Records and Tapes
  - Phonograph Record (3 45-R.P.M.s) (Box 763)
  - Tape (Box 763)
- Series XI: Campaign memorabilia, Miscellaneous
  - Congressional Record, Annotated. (Only those volumes with notes by Abzug /-- or members of her staff have (Box 763)
  - been retained in the collection.) (Box 763)
  - 64 hard-bound volumes, 1971-1972 (Box 763)
  - 36 paper-bound volumes, 1974-1976 2 unbound volumes, 1976 (Box 763)
- Series XII: Oversize
  - 1 folder. Items removed from Subject Files, Boxes 391, 396, 454, 458, 522, 563, 579 (Box 763)
  - 480 (Box 763)
  - Poster (Box 6)
  - Printed material - Manhattan Community Planning District 2: Greenwich Village (Box 669)
  - West Village, Little Italy (Box 669)
  - Printed material--List of military personnel missing or captured in S.E. Asia as of June 1976 (Box 669)
  - Four copies of a calendar called 'Lich A't Mao' 1975 FLAT BOX 669 Printed (Box 669)
  - material--Miracle Center Publicity (Box 669)
  - Printed material--Manhattan Vehicle Maintenance Facility: A feasibility study (Box 669)
  - for the U.S. Postal Service (Box 669)
  - Printed material- West-side Highway Project Environmental Impact Statement (Box 669)
  - Printed material- A comparison of the Senate and House versions ofH.R. 4073 to extend the (Box 669)
  - Appalachian Regional Development Act of 1965 (Box 669)
  - Printed material--S.502: Comparison between passed bill and the house Amendment thereto (Box 669)
  - Design report on the west-side highway (Box 669)
- Series XIII: Casework Files
  - Files on problems of individual constituents handled by Abzug's New York and Washington offices, 1971-1976. (Box 669)
  - New York Office File: (Box 764)
    - 1971 Chronological File (Box 764)
    - A--Z. (Box 765-779)
    - 1972 Chronological File (Box 780)
    - A-Z (Box 781-793)
    - 1973. Chronological File (Box 794)
    - A-Z (Box 795-807)
    - 1974. Chronological File. (Box 808)
    - A--Z (Box 809-822)
    - 1975. Chronological File (Box 823)
    - A--Z (Box 824-837)
    - 1976. Chronological File; Form Letters (Box 838)
    - A--Z (Box 839-857)
  - West Side Legislative Center. 1973--1976. A--Z (Box 858-861)
  - 181st Street District Office. A--Z (Box 862-867)
  - Washington Office: (Box 868-878)
    - 1971-1972. A--Z (Box 868-878)
    - 1973--1976. A--Z. (Box 879-896)
    - 1975--1976. A--Z (Box 897-899)
  - Military, 1971. A--Z. (Box 900-903)
  - Military, 1972 .A--Z (Box 904-905)
  - Military Academy Nominees, 1973--1976 (Box 906)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence and related material, 1971-1977 (Box 907-908)
  - Processing notes and index slips (OPEN) (Box 909)
- Series XIV: 1981 Addition
  - Files mentioned in the summary description for this addition that are not listed in Boxes 910-913 have been integrated into the original boxes listed above. For example. Box 63A contains the Abzug oral history memoir. (Box 909)
  - Pre and Post-Congressional Material: (Box 910)
  - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 910)
  - Campaigns, 1976--1978 (Box 910)
  - Civil Rights--Historical Material, 1952-1953 (Box 910)
  - Taxpayer s' Campaign for Urban Priorities, 1969 (Box 910)
  - Women's Strike for Equality, 1970 (Box 910)
  - Philadelphia Institute of Awareness Scrapbook. SEE OVERSIZE (Box 910)
  - Campaigns: (Box 911)
    - Mayoralty, 1977 (Box 911)
    - Senate, 1976 (Box 911)
  - Press Releases, 1971-1976 (Box 912)
  - Press Releases, 1970-1976 - Box 1107 (Box 912)
  - Press Releases, 1976 - Box 1108 (Box 912)
  - (12 Volumes in 2 R.S.C) (Box 912)
  - Press Clippings, 1970-1976 (Box 913)
  - Press Clippings March 1970--Sept 1972 (Box 1109)
  - Press Clippings Oct 1971--May 1973 (Box 1108)
  - Press Clippings April 1973--Dec 1973 (Box 1110)
  - Press Clippings Jan 1974--Nov 1974 (Box 1111)
  - Press Clippings July 1974--April 1975 (Box 1112)
  - Press Clippings May 1975--Jan 1976 (Box 1113)
  - Press Clippings Jan 1976--Aug 1976 (Box 1114)
  - Press Clippings July 1976--Aug 197 (Box 1115)
  - (72 Volumes in 2 R.S.C. and 6 GB)
- Series XV: 1986 Addition
  - Subseries XV.1: Correspondence
    - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 914)
    - Arranged correspondence: 1970-74; 1972, 1975 (Box 915)
    - Arranged correspondence: 1976, 1977 (Box 916)
    - Arranged correspondence: 1977 (Box 917)
    - Arranged correspondence: 1977 (Box 918)
    - Arranged correspondence: 1977 (Box 919)
    - Arranged correspondence: 1978-1981 (Box 920)
    - Arranged correspondence: 1979 (Box 921)
    - Arranged correspondence: 1979 (Box 922)
    - Arranged correspondence: 1979 (Box 925)
    - Arranged correspondence: 1980-1986 (Box 924)
  - Subseries XV.2: Administration
    Public Activities: Speaking invitations amp; requests; refusals; honoria; related correspondence
    - 1977 (Box 925)
    - 1977-78 (Box 926)
    - 1977, 1978 schedule work ups, 1977, 1978 (Box 927)
    - 1977, 1978 (Box 928)
    - 1978- 79 950 1979 (Box 929)
    - 1979 (Box 930)
    - 1979 (Box 931)
    - 1 October 1979-13 December 1979 (Box 932)
    - 18 December 1979-16 April 1980 (Box 933)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 934)
    - 17 April 1980-15 June 1980 (Box 935)
    - 19 June 1980-28 August 1980, 1981 refusals (Box 936)
    - 2 September 1980-18 December 1980 (Box 937)
    - 15 January 1981--7 March 1981 (Box 938)
    - 9 March 1981-15 May 1981 (Box 939)
    - 16 May 1981--29 October 1981 (Box 940)
    - 29 October 1981-19 February 1982 (Box 941)
    - 25 February 1982-25 May 1982 (Box 942)
    - 1 June 1982-50 December 1982 (Box 943)
    - 10 January 1982-17 October 1981 (Box 944)
    - 21 October 1985-7 March 1984 (Box 945)
    - 8 March 1984-14 August 1984 (Box 946)
    - 16 August 1984-15 November 1984 (Box 947)
    - 18 November 1984-22 April 1985 (Box 948)
    - 26 April 1985-27 August 1985 (Box 949)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 950)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 950A)
    - Public Activities: Schedules: (Box 951)
      - 1971 72 73 74 75
      - 1974 75 76 77 79 81 (Box 952)
      - 1976 79, 80, 81, 82 (Box 953)
    - Public Relations: Literary: (Box 954)
      - Gender Gap by Bella Abzug and Min Kelber (manuscripts, research materials, press clips)
      - Gender Gap --manuscripts (Box 955)
      - Gender Gap --miscellaneous (Box 956)
    - Press clippings:
      - 1968-77 (Box 957)
      - 1978 (Box 958)
      - 1978-80 (Box 959)
      - 1980-81 (Box 960)
      - 1980-86 (Box 961)
      - Miscellaneous press clips and photographs (Box 962)
  - Subseries XV.3: Subject Files--A through Z
    - Administration to Carter (Box 965)
    - China trip to Criminal Justice Reform Act of 1975 (Box 964)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1968, 1972 (Box 965)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1968, 1972, 1976, 1980 (Box 966)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1976, 1980, 1984 Election results (press, 1980) (Box 967)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1980 (Box 968-969)
    - Ellis Island to Political affairs (Box 970)
    - Political affairs to Women non-government organizations (Box 971)
    - WOMEN: International Women's Year (IWY) (Box 972-979)
    - WOMEN: IWY--1974,1975 (Box 980)
    - WOMEN: United Nations' IWY Conference, 19 June-2 July 1975 Mexico (Box 981)
    - WOMEN: IWY--New York State Meeting, July 1977 (Box 982)
    - WOMEN: IWY--Conference, 1977 Houston (Box 983)
    - WOMEN: IWY; National Advisor,. Committee on Women (NACW) (Box 984)
    - WOMEN: NACW (Box 985)
    - WOMEN: NACW, 1978 (Box 986-987)
    - WOMEN NACW, Carter's firing of Bella Abzug as co-chairperson (Box 988)
    - WOMEN: NACW; National Women's Political Caucus; Women against Pornography (Box 989)
    - Women against Rape
    - WOMEN: NWPC, pre-1970 to 1971 (Box 990)
    - WOMEN: NWPC, 1971-72 (Box 991)
    - WOMEN: NWPC, 1972 (Box 992)
      (includes correspondence with George McGovern)
    - WOMEN: NWPC, 1972-74 (Box 993)
    - WOMEN: NWPC, 1974-75 (Box 994)
    - WOMEN: NWPC ,1975-80 (Box 995)
    - WOMEN: NWPC, 1981 (Box 996)
    - WOMEN: (Box 997-1003)
    - WOMEN: Women Strike for Peace (WSP) (Box 1004-1005)
    - WOMEN: Women USA (Box 1006-1008)
    - WOMEN: World Conference of the United Nations' Decade for Women: Equality, Development and Peace (WCUNDW) 14--50 July 1980 Copenhagen (Box 1009)
    - WOMEN: WCUNDW, miscellaneous printed materials (Box 1010)
    - WOMEN: WCUNDW, Agenda items 5 through 10b; Conference background papers, 4 April-- 13 June 1980 (Box 1011)
    - WOMEN: WCUNDW, UN decisions concerning mid-decade conference; miscellaneous (Box 1012)
    - articles; agenda items; press releases Public Statements: press releases; speeches/remarks
    - Press releases, 1974 (Box 1013)
    - January--26 October 1975 (Box 1014)
    - 28 October 75--Cruise missile, 1976 (Box 1015)
    - Defense, 76--19 June 19176 (Box 1016)
    - 21 June 76--1S December 1976 (Box 1017)
    - Issues file, 1977 Speech records, 1970-74; press releases, 1972 (Box 1018)
    - Cable News Network airtime 1980-82 ( PRINTED MATERIAL) (Box 1019-1020)
    - Speeches, 1975 (Box 1021)
    - Speeches, 1974 (Box 1022)
    - Campaign '76: Senate race polls (Box 1023-1024)
    - Information banks, NY Times: 1969--7S; 1970-71; 1972-76 NY City Mayoral Primary Polls: (Box 1025)
    - 6/28/77 6/18/77 8/25/77
    - Printed materials: NY Congressional Poll, 17th C.D., 21-23 July 1982 (Box 1026)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 1027)
    - CAMPAIGNS: CONGRESS 1969-76; 1978, 1986 SENATE 1976 NYC MAYOR 1977
    - CONGRESS 1969--76; 1978, 1986
    - Congress 1970 (Box 1028)
    - Congress 1970-1976 (Box 1029)
    - Congress 1970-76 (Box 1050-1055)
    - Congress 1986 Subject file s B--W ,he (Box 1056-1057)
    - Congress '86: Schedules, July--November; Events, 8 Aug--27 September; Press; Past misc (Box 1058)
    - Congress '86: Schedules (daily) Sept--Nov; extras; primary schedules (Box 1059)
    - Congress '86: Events, 28 Sept-5 Nov (Box 1040)
    - Congress '86: Press releases; newsletters; printed materials; public relations (Box 1041)
  - Subseries XV.4: Senate 1976
    - Senate campaign, New York State (Box 1042-1056)
    - Miscellaneous Senate 1976 Congress 1970-78 (Box 1057)
  - Subseries XV.5: New York City Mayoral Campaign, 1977
    - Bella Literature (Box 1058)
    - Press releases, Sept; Subject files, A--E (Box 1059)
    - Press; Subject files, F--T S (Box 1060)
    - Press releases, 31 May-4 July 1977 (Box 1061)
    - Press releases, 5 July-5 August 1977 (Box 1062)
    - Press releases, 4 Aug-31 August 1977 (Box 1063)
    - Schedules, June-14 August lst 1977 (Box 1064)
    - Schedules, 15 August--7 September 1977 Miscellaneous printed materials (Box 1065)
    - Mayoralty 1977 (Box 1066-1070)
  - Subseries XV.6: Miscellaneous
    - Miscellaneous (Box 1071)
- Series XVI: Audio Visual Material
  - Subseries XVI.1: Speeches and Lectures
    - Better Bella (Box 1072)
    - As A Woman Songs by Jill Ridky 1 tape
    - Bella's Campaign song "Vote for Bella" by Irwing Crain Performed by composer 4 tapes
    - 19th Congressional Race "Victory Speech 1970-fall Nov 3rd 1 tape
    - Lecture given at Cornell "Election '84 Campaign Fair" 3/17/84, 1 tape
    - Address at Solidarity "Power of the Future Coalition" 3/3/81 1 tape
    - The Great NNATE Conference NYC 12/82 1 tape
    - "What makes Bella tick?" 9/14/81 1 tape
    - Women for BSA Luncheon 10/13/75 1 tape
    - St. Joseph's College, Conn. 4/11/83 1 tape
    - Abzug/Schlesinger /Weighart-WMCA 1 tape
    - Reid Lectures Luncheon 11/13/79 1 tape
    - Action message Heems-Hatch 8/24/82 1 tape
    - Marymount Manhattan Public Policy Breakfast Dotty Lynch/Kathy Frank: 12/6/84: 1 tape
    - Society of Women Engineers. Award Banquet 6/79 1 tape
    - Susan B Anthony Lectures April '81- Hartford 1 tape
    - BSA Voice exercises 1 tape
    - Educational tape-BSA 1 tape
    - District conference- BSA 1 tape
    - Cay political Union Debaue--BSA v. Ramsey Clarke 1975 1 tape
    - Federal Bar Association 5/75 1 tape
    - "Tribute to Our Unions" Volume 11 12/6/75 1 tape
    - "Tribute to our Unions Volume 10 12/6/75 2 tapes a and b
    - Pines Home 6/4/72 1 tape
    - USC of Performing Arts 1/11/83 1 tape
    - Univ. of Purdue 2/6/81 "Women in Politics" III 1 tape
    - Univ. of Purdue "Women in Politics" #3 2/6/81 1 tape
    - "Women in Crisis" 1/79
    - "Women in Politics; A Personal Perspective" 11/13/79 1 tape
    - I.I.A. (CW) '75 or '76 1 tape
    - Hawaii: New Years Message 12/19/81 (Included: BSA 12/4/80) 1 tape
    - New Pa1tz Graduation Speech 6/75
    - Alleghery College 1/7/85
    - Bella's first appearance on the steps of the Capital 1971 1 tape
    - BSA WSP 12/5/[?] 1 tape
    - Jewish Federation of Omaha 4/2/81 1 tape
    - National Farmers Union Ladies F1y-N 5/22/73
    - BSA Interchange Seminar 7/21/79 1 tape
    - On the Draft 5/6/[?] 1 tape
    - On the Draft 4/21-23 [?] 1 tape
    - BSA Anti-Draft Rally 3/17-21/80 1 tape
    - BSA at platform committee/Colman Young 4/10/80 1 tape
    - Kosher breakfast 8/3/76 campaign 1 tape
    - Israel: POW's 12/13/73 1 tape
    - Jewish Festivals for Life-d.c. Temple Sinai 1/16/73 1 tape
    - Israel 1 tape
    - Jewish Defense League 10/28/[?] 3 tape set
    - Reply to survey on Women Political Candidates running for office--Patsy Mink 6/10/83 1 tape
    - 20th C.D. Comm. Congo Abzug, Furness, Abzug, Congress 5/5/73 1 tape
    - Conference closing 6/12/80 1 tape
    - "Politics and Power" 2/6/79 Minneapolis
    - Nairobi women's conference WOR Radio 7: 10 am 1 tape
    - B.A. Keynote speech Conference of Cincinnati Women 1 tape
    - YWCA of Worcester Mass 100th Annual Meeting 6/17/85 Mechanics Hall 1 tape
    - Beth EI Temple Springfield Mass M 2 tapes
    - "Closing the Power Gap April 20, 85 Buffolo NY Erie community college, city campus 1 tape
    - Presidential Seminar 4/25/76 112 Staten Island Comm. College Host: Dr. Birenbaul 1 tape
    - 7/17/84-NWPC 1 tape
    - My Freedom Song, Phil Muccigrosso Crusader, The Flaming Eagle Agen '7-11' 1 tape
    - Psychiatric Recorder Men and Women 1 tape
    - University of Ill. Urbana-Chamagne 7/3/85 1 tape
    - Up the Escalator: A look back at the Jewish Comm. of the Bronx Produced by Johanna Cooper Nat'l End for Arts
  - Radio and T.V.
    - News conference Labor comm. for Moynihan Hotel Biltmooe 7/21/76 1 tape
    - A.M. New York Show Campaign '76 1 tape
    - Campaign for Carter by Women BSA v Clark 7/12/76 1 tape
    - Regional ECO Dev. Banks and Support DPM WNBC TV 1976 1 tape
    - James Buckley WCBS TV Newsmakers 9/5/79 1 tape
    - Newsmakers Moynihan on WCBS TV 7/5/76 1 tape
    - Channel 31 "At Issue" 1976 Campaign Ramsey Clark and Paul O'Dwyer 1 tape
    - Moynihan WCBS FM Campaign Fonda, Women v. Carter 7/11/76 1 tape
    - Campaign women's caucus and Drive: Montano, Santiago, Badillo, on DPM BSA AND Lily T.
    - 7/13/76 1 tape
    - Campaign June 10 Mostly Moynihan 1976 1 tape
    - Campaign
    - BSA Campaign, Buckley GOP Convention ICC, ACA meet reacts to DPM Welfare 1 tape
    - BSA Campaign 9/13/76 WNET Debate and t.v. coverage " 1 tape
    - BSA Campaign Day care. DPM on CBS 6/7--6/29 3 endorsements 1 tape
    - Meeting with upstate press campaign with breakfast 7/76 1 tape
    - Campaign-Moynihan on Bob Grant show ICA 6/2/76 1 tape (Box 1073)
    - Barry Farber Show WMCA Kroeger and Lena 1 tape
    - Barry Farber Show WMCA--9/24 Bill Kroeger, Marin Martinez and Earnest Herbert (WOR) 1 tape' a ;"
    - Barry Farber show 9/24 WMCA War Robert Fifkino. Attorney Bookd on G.I. Rights
    - 10/7/70 1 tape
    - Barry Farber Show WOR 8:15 10/27 1 tape
    - Barry Farber Show WOR 10/29 Rabbi Shulem Rvben and Chertov Lodico 1 tape
    - Barry Farber Show WOR 9/24 Taxi driver deaths 1 tape
    - Barry Farber Show WOR 9/25 Billy Harper. Marker Davis (jazz musicians) 1 tape
    - Barry Farber Show WOR 10/26 8:15; 1 tape
    - Barry Farber Show WOR 9/17 Political Program 1 tape
    - Barry Farber Show WOR 10/22 1 tape
    - Barry Farber Show WOR 10/21 8:15 Charges Bella with calling him a liar! 1 tape
    - Barry Gray Show Jan 20 '76 BSA 1 tape
    - Barry Farber WOR Guest: Former Senator Clark of Penn. 9/28 1 tape
    - Campaign 7-2 Boat ride. Newman, Shawn and Sokol 1 tape
    - Barry Gray Show WMCA 9/9/70 11pm 1 tape
    - Barry Gray Show 6/16/72 Kretchin and Newfield? 1 tape
    - "Impeachment? " Contact Paul Meisaac WBAI-FM " 1 tape
    - WABS RADIO 1 tape
    - WBAI-BSA 1 tape
    - Michael Jackson Show 2/17/83 KABC Set of 3 tapes
    - Direct News Special Edition 1/2 "The Politics of the Atom" 1 tape
    - Barry Gray; Abzug v. Farber; BSA on abortion 9/9/70 1 tape
    - WVHY-FM 2/2/79 1 tape
    - Drug addiction; a day with Bella 9/14/79 7:30 pm interview 1 tape
    - Barry Gray Show; "Congresswoman Elect" '70 1 tape
    - HIP Forum; Pia Lindstrom NBC-TV For: Mr. Horowitz (3 cuts) 11/25/74
    - Barry Gray Show BSA 1 tape
    - WPIX T.V. Debate 9/2/76 1 tape
    - KPFK Radio; Beverly Wilshire Hotel; mecca meeting 2/17/82 1 tape
    - ABC News "Issues and Answers" After Presidential firing 1/14/79 1 tape
    - Sage talk show 5/14/75 3 tape set
    - WBAI Produced zalisk; APA 9/27/79 1 tape
    - Larry King Show BSA Q.20/84 12-1pm 1 tape (A)
    - Larry King Show;BSA 4/20/S4, 1 tape
    - Channel 7 ABC B.A. 10/29/70 1 tape
    - '72 Primary against Ryan WOR "Dean Show" 1 tape
    - 1/8/85 B'Nai B'Rith Press conference Washington D.C. 1 tape
    - BSA in Waterville Maine 4/22/85 Lorimer Chapel 1 tape
    - March 21.85 Kingsborough Community College NY Women's History Month Celebration Intro: Prof Terry Trilling: 1 tape
    - BSA U. of Penn. 3-16-85 1 tape
    - Medicaid Abortions- Rhonda Copeland 2/24/S2: Issues 1 Tape
    - Abortion debate in the senate 1 tape
    - Abortion victory 1 tape
    - Gloria Steinem on Abortion 1/15/S0 1 tape
    - Planned Parenthood; Joanne Howes; 4/15/S3; 1 tape
    - Planned Parenthood; Joanne Howes 9/2S/S1 (hatch anti-abortion) 1 tape
    - ERA stay; equal education threat 2/3/S2 1 tape
    - ERA: Ellie Smeal 5/7/S0 1 tape
    - Tsongas/ERA 1 tape
    - The ERA In America 29 seconds 1 tape
    - Jean Young 1 tape
    - National Advisory Council Title IX 1 tape
    - Women Against Violence, Porno., and Media 11/17/81 Lily Mar 1 tape
    - Women Against War; end of B. Williams/Gloria Steinem; 6/17/S0 1 tape
    - Rep. Mary Rose Oakar 4/80 Social Security 1 tape
    - Congo Dakar 9/26/83 Social Security 1 tape
    - Social Security; Abortion; Pam Elam 7/4/81
    - Fair Insurance Practice Marv Gray-Weal; 1 tape
    - White house conference on aging; 1 tape
    - Working women Hawaii 2/16/S2 1 tape
    - Vietnam; Bombing of Cambodia; Domestic cuts; WINS 1/14/73 1 tape
    - Vietnam and Nixon; Before Pres. Election; Cooper Union; '72 1 tape
    - Draft Resistance Trial; & support statements; 1 tape
    - Church conference with Bella 2 tapes
    - Gloria Steinem NWPC 7/15/79 1 tape. BSA NWPC 7/15/79 36B 1 tape
    - NWPC Closing Sunday; Belia 7/15/79
    - NWPC; Opening ceremony BSA Cincinatti Oil. k-2S Part 1 7/14/79
    - Alva Myrrdal Press Conference 5/26/80
    - NYC Message PDNYC May Dorfman 8/12/82 2 tapes
    - American women on the move Joanne Rosenzweig; 1 tape
    - Conon Families Patsy Mink 1 tape
    - Big Business Day (84 sec. B. Ledbetter; Patsy Mink; 1 tape
    - Conservative candidate; Christina Wilson; 1 tape
    - Kickoff Campaign Petition; 1 tape
    - Caucus Report; 2 tapes
    - AFSCME- San Jose; 1 tape
    - Joyce Miller 10/28/80 1 tape
    - Coleman Meeting 3/12/76 02; 1 tape
    - Miriam Friedlander 9/29 Press Conference: 1 Tape
    - NWPC Ferraro, Etc. July 7 1 tape (Box 1074)
    - NWPC San Antonio #1 Tobias Leader Farley; 1 tape
    - NWPC San Antonio #3 Hoeber; 1 tape
    - Farber-Greenwich House; Candidate Night 10/13/70 1 tape
    - Meeting with Coleman Part 2 3/12/76 1 tape
    - ANN Richards at Elected Official Banquet July 8; 1 tape
    - Marion Wright Edelman 3/2S/83; 1 tape
    - Panel on the Right to Transportation 20th CD CommCon5/4/74; 1 tape
    - Linda Lavin; NCWW; 1 tape
    - Yamasalci 5/9/80; 1 tape
    - Rules Comm. and National Constitution Demo. Party Spring '76 1 tape